Exercise 10-6. The Middle Eye List. The letter I in the unstressed position
devolves consistently into a schwa. Repeat. Ability. Accident. Accountability.
Activity. Adversity. America. Analytical. Animal. Applicant. Application. Article.
Astronomical. Audible. Auditor. availability, beautiful, brutality,
calamity, California, candidate, capacity, celebrity, charity, Christianity,
clinical, clerical, chemical, chemistry, chronological, clarity, commodity,
community, communication, complexity, Confident. Confidentiality. Contribution.
Creativity. Credit. Critical. Cubicle. Curiosity. Difficult. Dignity. Disparity.
Diversity. Edison. Editor. Electricity. Eligibility. Eliminated. Engineer.
Episode. Equality. Evidence. Experiment. Facility. Familiarity. Feasibility.
Flexibility. Florida. Foreigner. Formality. Fraternity. Gravity. Heredity.
hospitality, hostility, humanity, humidity, humility, identity, imitation,
immaturity, immigration, immunity, incident, individuality, infinity,
insecurity, instability, institute, investigation, invisible, invitation,
Janitor. Jennifer. Legalization. Liability. Madison. Maturity. Medicine.
Mentality. Majority. Maximum. Michigan. Minimum. Minority. Modify. Monica.
Monitor. Municipality, Nationality, Naturalization, Necessity, Negative,
Nomination, Opportunity, Organization, Partiality, Physical, Pitiful, Politics,
Positive, Possible, Possibility, President. Principle. Priority.
Psychological. Publicity. Qualify. Quality. Quantity. Radical. Reality.
Rectify. Resident. Responsibility. Sacrifice. Sanity. Security. Seminar.
Seniority. Severity. Sensitivity. Similar. Skeptical. Superiority. Technical.
Testify. Typical. Uniform. Unity. University. Validity. Visitor.